Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/balraj-rai (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Figma (Software)
Responsive Web Design
Product Design

Balraj Rai

Product Designer at Tide

London, England, United Kingdom

Summary

User Experience Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the design industry. Skilled in Research, User Testing, Wireframing, Prototyping, and High Fidelity Design. Strong arts and design professional graduated in Architecture from the University of East London and in UX Design from General Assembly.

Experience

Tide

Product Designer March 2023 - Present (8 months)

London, England, United Kingdom

Funding Options - Acquired by Tide Product Designer June 2022 - February 2023 (9 months) London, England, United Kingdom

Raspberry Pi Foundation
Product Designer
May 2020 - September 2021 (1 year 5 months)
Cambridge, England, United Kingdom

Ford Motor Company
UX Designer
December 2019 - February 2020 (3 months)
London, United Kingdom

Bose Corporation
Store Sales Manager (via Channel Assist)
April 2019 - July 2019 (4 months)
Heathrow Airport, London, England, United Kingdom

Google

Smart Home Product Expert (via Gekko Group) October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months)

London, England, United Kingdom

SSC Architecture
Architectural Assistant Part 1
June 2018 - December 2018 (7 months)
London, England, United Kingdom

Education

University of East London
Bachelor of Architecture - BArch, Architecture

The Intrapreneurs Club
UX Design Accelerator Programme · (2020)

General Assembly
User Experience Design · (2019)

University of Greenwich

Bachelor of Architecture - BArch